[{"answer": "Why? What's wrong with the subject? This is a bad subject", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "It's not that I want to keep talking about it? just think that the subject should resolve itself based on its own momentum", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Oh, nothin'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Well, what do you want me to do", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Well, you don't seem too enthused about the whole thing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Well, at least have some reaction to it", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Well, what do you want me to do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, I don't", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, please! That is the last thing that I want", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, right", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Jerr", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yeah, that's right. I don't wanna get married", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, that's right. I don't wanna get married", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, you come on", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yeah, I probably have. Yeah, of course I have. What am I talking about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Extend the doors on the toilet stalls at Yankee Stadium to the floor ...door comes down. Hides your feet. Yes. I like it. I like it a lot", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I think it's fantastic. I think it's a fantastic idea", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Yes, I do", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "That's allowed? You're allowed to postpone it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "So, I could do that", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You're kidding", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You would turn me in", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What kind of person are you going around killing people", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well,, if you'll kill this person, who's to say I wouldn't be next", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, for example, say there's a forest, . . ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You know my temple has many single functions", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Good, good day. How was your day", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "The Lowers, really", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No, I want to go", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No, I want to go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, nothin' much, . . . talkin'. . . . Oh, oh, oh, did I have an unbelievable idea today", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Sstill love. Still love", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "No no no, no mistake, no mistake. No, no , listen, we're going to get married over Christmas, I ...It doesn't make any difference to me. It's fine. Really", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Well, at least you probably had some, uh, pretty good mak", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You didn't have mak", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I didn't have any sex", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I didn't have mak", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Did you here that? I can't believe this he's eating his sandwich", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "This is amazing.  Thank you. Thank you very much. . . . I'm going back in! . . . You'll feel better", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I hope she's feeling better", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "She didn't tell you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Good, good day. How was your day", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Oh, nothing much. You know, I went over to my friend's. Talked to my friend. Um, could I talk to you for a minute", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Nothing, nothing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yes he did", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "It didn't take much prodding either, I must say", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "He did it", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "No, no. Listen, Rabbi, I'd like to ask you a question. Why, why did you tell my friend my friend what I talked to you about", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Of course it was a problem for me. . . . You didn't, you didn't tell anyone else about this, did you", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Suing? What for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "It's supposed to be hot", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "The coffee was too hot", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Postponement.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Not THAT hot.", "qsentId": 54}]